the-female-orgasm.com 2014-05-16

# The Female Orgasm :: Your Privacy Is Paramount

**Privacy Policy**

Any and all information collected at this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, loaned, or otherwise disclosed. Any information you give to The-Female-Orgasm.com will be held with the utmost care, and will not be used in ways to which you have not consented. We do not spam.

**Scope**

This document replaces all previous documents including to but not limited to previous registration agreements, online registrations, and any other method used or developed to grant access to The-Female-Orgasm.com member area. This policy applies to all users of The-Female-Orgasm.com and all Femorg.com Ltd. sites. The term "The-Female-Orgasm.com services" defines the total environment, and includes, but is not limited to, the The-Female-Orgasm.com web site, FemorgLLC.com and Femorg.com Ltd. and their email system, database, documentation and content.

**IP Address & Browser Information**

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. Your IP address is used to help identify you, to gather broad demographic information, and to protect both you and us in the event of fraudulent or unauthorized transactions.

**Information Collection & Use**

The customer contact information is also used to contact the visitor only when necessary or beneficial to you. This site contains links to other sites - The-Female-Orgasm.com and Femorg.com Ltd. are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other such websites. Selection of an ad banner or link may redirect you to a third party web site. Transactions that occur between the you and such third party's are strictly between the you and the third party and are not the responsibility of Femorg.com Ltd. Because Femorg.com Ltd. is not responsible for the availability of these outside resources or their privacy policy or content, you should direct any concerns regarding any external link to that sites administrator or webmaster.

**Subscription Data**

We collect visitor's contact information (including E-mail addresses), and financial information (including account or credit card numbers) only when subscribers use our "alternate billing" system. Contact information from the order form is used to send orders, information about our company, and promotional material from some of our partners to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Financial information that is collected is only used to check the users' qualifications and to bill the user for products and services ordered. These payments may be processed through third party billers, including CCBill, Epoch and others. Some information submitted to third party billers may be made available to Femorg.com Ltd. for administrative purposes. See the privacy policy on the actual payment page for detailed information about the policies of a specific third party biller.

**Resale or Disclosure of Information to Third Parties**

Femorg.com Ltd. does not sell, rent, loan, trade, or lease any personal information collected at our site, including email addresses and/or IM addresses, and/or "profiles". Customer names will not be sold. We will not share your information with third parties although Femorg.com Ltd. completely abides by law and will respond to subpoenas, warrants or other court orders regarding information of a particular visitor. Additionally, if a member is believed to be engaged in illegal activity, we reserve the right to report this to the appropriate law enforcement bodies. 

Please note: This section expressly applies to your personal information that we may collect, and not to the actual content of your personals profile and any other information that you choose to make publicly visible on Femorg.com Ltd. web sites. Of course, if you choose to disclose personal information in your profile or communications with other Femorg.com Ltd. website members, that information will be disclosed to third parties.

**Links**

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by The-Female-Orgasm.com website.

**Correcting & Updating Personal Information**

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as billing information), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. This can usually be done at the member information page, or by emailing our Customer Support.

**Other**

Subscribers may gain consenting access to our fora, message boards, and/or news groups. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
